

## **Profile**

I am a web developer who specializes in JavaScript programming language and extended my skills with Typescript. I have a lot of experience as a Microsoft developer and therefore have extensive knowledge with React, SharePoint, Azure and Microsoft Teams. I am proficient in using PowerShell to automate and manage these technologies. My skills enable me to design and develop powerful and integrated web applications specifically tailored to meet the required needs and integrations.

# **Employment History**

#### Microsoft developer, Netmedia, Saarbrücken

FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Web App Developer proficient in React, Typescript, Microsoft SharePoint, Teams, Microsoft Graph, and PowerShell for efficient and collaborative solutions.

#### Full-stack JavaScript Developer, FindQuickly, Sarreguemines

SEPTEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022

Skilled Full-stack JavaScript Developer proficient in React, Node.js, and Express. Expertise in building scalable web applications with a focus on delivering high-quality solutions.

#### Metalworker, Hand Leffer GmbH, Saarbrücken

AUGUST 2011 - JULY 2020

#### Non-commissioned officer, Armée de Terre, Sarrebourg

DECEMBER 2008 - NOVEMBER 2011

## **Education**

### Web developer internship, FindQuickly, Sarreguemines

FEBRUARY 2021 - AUGUST 2021

Learn javascript full-stack development with MySQL and MongoDB databases.

#### Bachelor's degree, Esecad, Montrouge

SEPTEMBER 2020 — SEPTEMBER 2021

Web developer training

#### **Self-training**

JANUARY 2018 - PRESENT

Web applications developer

## A-level commerce, Lycée Simon Lazard, Sarreguemines

SEPTEMBER 2005 - JULY 2008

## **Details**

Puttelange-aux-Lacs
France
+33 6 45 92 26 14
hp.hectorpascal@gmail.com

#### Links

My portfolio

LinkedIn

CodeSandBox

<u>CodePen</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

### Skills

Sass

**JavaScript** 

**TypeScript** 

React

Microsoft architecture

PowerShell

Node

MySQL

Git

## Languages

French

German

**English** 

## **Hobbies**

Diving Programming Hiking